{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of using JavaScript?",
            "answer": [
                "Client-side JavaScript does not allow the reading or writing of files.",
                "JavaScript can not be used for Networking applications because there is no such support available.",
                "JavaScript doesn't have any multithreading or multiprocess capabilities.",
                "All of the above."
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to create a cookie using JavaScript?",
            "answer": [
                "document.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
                "browser.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
                "window.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
                "navigator.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';"
            ],
            "correct": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following type of variable is visible only with a function where it is defined?",
            "answer": [
                "global variable",
                "local variable",
                "Both of the above",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which built-in method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?",
            "answer": [
                "substr()",
                "getSubstring()",
                "slice()",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of Number object returns the number's value?",
            "answer": [
                "toString()",
                "valueOf()",
                "toLocaleString()",
                "toPrecision()"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating whether a reference string comes before or after or is the same as the given string in sort order?",
            "answer": [
                "localeCompare()",
                "search()",
                "substr()",
                "concat"
            ],
            "correct": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to upper case?",
            "answer": [
                "toLocaleUpperCase()",
                "toUpperCase()",
                "toString()",
                "substring()"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?",
            "answer": [
                "fixed()",
                "fontcolor()",
                "fontsize()",
                "italics()"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of Array object adds one or more eleements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
            "answer": [
                "pop()",
                "push()",
                "join()",
                "map()"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of Array object adds one or more elements to the front of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
            "answer": [
                "unshift()",
                "sort()",
                "spice()",
                "toString()"
            ],
            "correct": "0"
        }
    ]
}